IBT0060
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Benefits Department Records-Summary Plan Descriptions, 1944-2000; Series 1; This collection consists of summary plan descriptions (SPDs) for regional and/or local union organizations of the IBT. SPDs generally spell out the condiditons of coverage and the details of various benefits - life insuran
  - Central Pennsylvania Teamsters, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Central States, Southeast and Southwest Areas, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Central Pennsylvania, ND (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Denver Grocers Health Benefits Plan, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Central States, Southeast and Southwest Areas, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - East Bay Drayage Drivers, 1993-1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Local 863, ND (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Graphics Communications National, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Local 992, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Local 557, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Local 331, 206-2006 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Minnesota Teamsters, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Local 701, ND (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Local 812, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Minnesota Teamsters, ND (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Local 331, 1999-2005 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Local 170, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Local 122, ND (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Local 252, ND (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Local 277, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Local 348, ND (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - A&P Shopwell, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Local 631, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Southern California Bakery Drivers, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Southwestern Teamsters, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Local 617, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Local 435, 2003-2004 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Local 404, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Local 638, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Local 97, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Retiree's Welfare Trust, 2003-2006 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Local 522, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Local 816, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Local 738, ND (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Local 1205, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Local 804, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Local 830, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Local 456, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Inland Empire, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Local 70, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - East Bay Dryage Drivers, 1993- 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland Bakers and Teamsters, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Local 738, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Washington Teamsters, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Washington Teamsters, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Local 676, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Local 331, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Local 485, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Local 348, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Joint Council 28, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - New York State Teamsters, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - New York State Teamsters, ND (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Ohio Conference, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Local 707, ND (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Ohio Teamsters, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Retiree's Welfare Trust, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - San Diego County, 2003 -2005 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Local 945, ND (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Security Trust Fund, 1997-2001 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - iscellaneous Security Trust Fund, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Local 707, ND (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Retired Employees Medicare Trust, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Local 856, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Local 945, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Food Industry Members, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Local 102, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Local 142, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Local 469, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Local 456, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Local 830, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Local 716, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Local 52, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Teamsters National, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Local 727, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Local 572, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Local 418, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Local 837, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Local 572, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Local 856, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Utah Idaho, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Utah Idaho, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Local 142, 1997-2008 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Local 727, ND (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Local 856, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters Managed, 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Local 830, ND (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Local 1164, ND (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Security Trust Fund, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Security Trust Fund, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Local 73, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Local 854, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Local 522, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Southwestern Teamsters, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Southern California, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Southern Region, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Local 52, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Local 142, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Local 854, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Local 557, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Local 522, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Local 33, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Local 251, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Local 404, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Local 170, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Local 638, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Local 277, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Local 170, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Local 346, 2004-2007 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Central Pennsylvania, 1996-2004 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Local 804, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Local 1205, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Western Pennsylvania, 2001-2007 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Local 781, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - IBT Affiliates Pension Fund Brochurea, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - IBT Retiree Affairs Department Pension Fund Brochures, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Health Plan Brochures, Undated; Series 1 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Parking Division Contact Card, 2016; Series 1 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Teamsters Aviation Mechanics License Protection Program, Undated; Series 1 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Teamsters Legal Defense Fund, Circa 2012; Series 1 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Veteran Assistance, Undated; Series 1 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 20)
  - ACA and Healthcare Bargaining, Undated; Series 1 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Members Benefits, Undated; Series 1 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Teamster Privilege - Benefits for you, 2014; Series 1 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 22)